repco.com.au 2006-06-18

# Repco Corporation Limited - Privacy Policy

| 

|   
  
---|---  
  
Privacy Policy

Disclaimer

While Repco has endeavoured to ensure that all information provided on Repco Internet websites is accurate and up to date, Repco takes no responsibility for any error or omission relating to this information. To the maximum extent permitted by law, Repco will not be liable for any cost, loss or damage suffered by you through your use of Repco's Internet websites or Repco's failure to provide access to these Internet websites or information updates.

Use of the website is governed by the Repco website Terms and Conditions of Use. 

Online Privacy Policy

This online Privacy Policy is provided to make you aware of how Repco collects uses and manages information of visitors to its Internet websites. Repco view the personal privacy of users as an important issue, and are committed to maintaining the security of personal information provided to Repco by users in accessing repco.com.au . This policy forms part of the terms of use of the website, and describes how Repco treats personal information that it receives through your use of the website.

[Please note] Repco makes some other websites available to you from hyperlinks in repco.com.au. These websites are not subject to Repco's Privacy Policy. You should review the privacy policy of each individual website you access via hyperlinks from this website, and assess whether the policy of each website is satisfactory to you before you use the other websites.

What Information Do We Collect and How Is It Used?

Repco collects the following information regarding visitors to our website: domain name, name, information regarding what pages are accessed, information volunteered by you, such as feedback information, e-mail address, and your preferred means of communication. Repco collects and logs this information for communication purposes.

Other than stated in the preceding, no attempt is made to identify users or their browsing activities except, in the event of an investigation, where a law enforcement agency may exercise a warrant to inspect logs, or where Repco believes it is required to collect and produce relevant electronic documentation to fulfill its obligations to third parties, including statutory organizations under local law.

Repco endeavors to use and disclose your personal information only in limited circumstances. Repco will do so if it is necessary to protect any copyright or intellectual property in the material in the website, or if it is necessary to enforce the Repco website 

Terms and Conditions of Use.

Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that a website may write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information, such as a userID, that the website uses to track the pages you have visited. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you personally supply. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other websites.

repco.com.au websites use cookies to track user traffic patterns and to better serve you when you revisit the website. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, providing you with the opportunity to either accept or reject it. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser. 

Security

Repco takes all reasonable security measures to protect personal information from loss, unauthorized access, destruction, misuse, modification or disclosure. As far as permissible under law, Repco accepts no responsibility for the unauthorized access of personal information held by Repco.

Subscription Services

Repco offers a free subscription service so that you may receive information about Repco by e-mail. While Repco endeavors to provide you with this information on a timely basis, Repco cannot guarantee that delivery by e-mail will not be unavoidably delayed.

Updating this Privacy Policy

The content of this Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time, so we suggest that you return to the website on a regular basis and carefully read the information provided.
